<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="arr_debate">
		<item>GMF The Impact on Irish Agriculture</item>
		<item>Nutrition/Allergies</item>
		<item>Obesity</item>
		<item>Developing World</item>
		<item>Food and Tourism</item>
		<item>How Irish is your food: Agriculture in the West of Ireland</item>
		<item>Future of Fisheries</item>
		<item>Food Safety in Modern Times</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="arr_talk">
		<item>How to feed a family on a budget</item>
		<item>Cooking for fussy eaters</item>
		<item>Galway and the famine</item>
		<item>Sustainable Cities</item>
		<item>Galwlay and the wine trade</item>
		<item>How to run a community garden</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="arr_taste">
		<item>Smoked Salmon and whiskey</item>
		<item>Honey and Meale</item>
		<item>West of Ireland Cheese</item>
		<item>The Great Irish Black Puddings</item>
		<item>Craft Beer From Ireland</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="arr_chil">
		<item>Animals at the Museum</item>
		<item>Bread making</item>
		<item>Honey in the City</item>
		<item>Jam making / Butter making</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="arr_other">
		<item>The Harvest Food Market</item>
		<item>Galway\'s Food Community</item>
		<item>The Big Award</item>
		<item>The Feast</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- Debate -->
	<string-array name="arr_gmf">
		<item>GMF The Impact on Irish Agriculture</item>
		<item>Unknown</item>
		<item>IFA (confirmed)</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="arr_nutrition">
		<item>Nutrition/Allergies</item>
		<item>Jackie Jones</item>
		<item>Have we inflicted allergies upon ourselves, and how do we deal with them?\nThis debate will discuss the issue of how allergies have been caused and why they are becoming more prevalent in our society.\nThe debate will address whether we can prevent the spread of allergies, and how to deal with them.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="arr_obesity">
		<item>Obesity</item>
		<item>Sarah Burke health policy analyst (Rte/TV3)</item>
		<item>Our children are now 4 st heavier than in the 1970\'s: Should we as a nation be concerned about this? Is it our governments reponsibility to intervene? What are the contributing factors: education/food poverty?</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="arr_developing">
		<item>Developing Word</item>
		<item>Patrick Towers</item>
		<item>What are the main causes of food poverty in the global environment? How does access to resources affect the distribution of food aid in stricken countries?\nWhat is the relationship of Global economic systems to food poverty?\nWhat can be done on a local level?</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="arr_tourism">
		<item>Food and Tourism</item>
		<item>Ella McSweeney, agriculture and food journalist</item>
		<item>Why do people travel to Ireland? The people, the culture, and the Guinness?\nTourism figures point to a trend of walking, fishing, golfing, and cycling holidays. However no matter the purpose they must all eat, and meanwhile the Irish culinary world is making its mark with the best sourced and presented food.\nOur panel will look at the comodity of Irish food, and why we undersell ourselves when it comes to Irish food.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="arr_agriculture">
		<item>How Irish is your food: Agriculture in the West of Ireland</item>
		<item>Kevin Sheridan, Sheridans Cheesemongers</item>
		<item>IFA, Professor Michael Cuddy NUIG, Teagasc, ICMSA, Kevin Sheridan\nWhat is the future for agriculture in Ireland?\nCan samll producers work together to create a viable and sustainable market for their products?</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="arr_fisheries">
		<item>Future of Fisheries</item>
		<item>Frank Flemmings</item>
		<item>What is the true cost of fish in a modern Ireland?\nWhat impact will our fishing practices have on the future of the Irish fishing industry?\nWhy is there an ocean bursting with incredibly tasty fish that we will not eat because we have never heard them?\nA debate on the current state of the fisheries, where it is going, and at what cost to customers, businesses and industry in Ireland.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="arr_safety">
		<item>Food Satety in Modern Times</item>
		<item>Proff. Martin McCormican</item>
		<item>Blank</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<!--
		 Talks 
	-->
	<string-array name="talk_1">
		<item>How to feed a family on a budget</item>
		<item>A samll budget should never mean a compromise on quality and health. This talk will focus on feeding the family a wholesome and tasty weekly menu when on a budget.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="talk_2">
		<item>Cooking for fussy eaters</item>
		<item>Every parent has to deal with it at some stage, and many of us have witnessed it at dinner parties. It is not easy to change the mindset of fussy eaters, but we can work around them. Come and check out ingenious ways to get the fussy eater to eat greens.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="talk_3">
		<item>Galway and the famine</item>
		<item>How did the famine affect our ancestors? Come to the Galway museum to discover how the famine affected the towns people of Galway both rich and poor. From within the city walls, to the fishing village of the Claddagh.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="talk_4">
		<item>Sustainable Cities</item>
		<item>How as a city can we learn to be more sustainable, and provide for ourselves into the future, and what are we currently doing, if anything to ensure Galway is a sustainable city.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="talk_5">
		<item>Galwlay and the wine trade</item>
		<item>The great port of Galway was once a bustling wine port, this talk will delve into the ports rich history in the wine trade, and reveal commodity long lost in the city.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="talk_6">
		<item>How to run a community garden</item>
		<item>With a great increase in home grown and community gardens this talk will reveal everything to set up your very own community garden, when to pant, when to weed, and you need to get started.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- 
		Talks 
	-->
	<string-array name="taste_1">
		<item>Smoked Salmon and whiskey</item>
		<item>Sample a selection of smoked salmon from smokeries inthe West of Ireland matched with Irish Whiskeys</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="taste_2">
		<item>Honey and Meale</item>
		<item>A chance to meet and taste some of the unique honeys produced in the Burren and West of Ireland accompained by a glass of meade. Not to mention the delicious combination of honey and blue cheese.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="taste_3">
		<item>West of Ireland Cheese</item>
		<item>Come along and sample some of the finest cheeses from the West of Ireland, paired with beers, wine and local breads.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="taste_4">
		<item>The Great Irish Black Puddings</item>
		<item>A chance to taste some of Irelands few remanining fresh blood puddings and to meet their makers: Ed Hick (Co. Dublin), Jack McCarthy (Kanturk), and Seamus Kelly (Newport).</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="taste_5">
		<item>Craft Beer From Ireland</item>
		<item>The reassendence of craft brewing in Ireland will be on display, Here you will have a change to taste the new craft beers from Dungarvan, Belfast, Carlow, Cork, and of course our own Galway Hooker.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- 
		Children
	-->
	<string-array name="chil_1">
		<item>Animals at the Museum</item>
		<item>The festival will feature a selection of children’s workshops and demonstrations over the weekend, with a focus on introducing children to the world of food in a practical hands on way. Bring your children to discover how honey is made, join in the bread making workshop, and make your own butter and jam.\n\n<b>Animals at the Museum.</b> A Portable petting farm will be based outside the museum on Saturday and Sunday afternoon.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="chil_2">
		<item>Bread making</item>
		<item>The festival will feature a selection of children’s workshops and demonstrations over the weekend, with a focus on introducing children to the world of food in a practical hands on way. Bring your children to discover how honey is made, join in the bread making workshop, and make your own butter and jam.\n<b>Bread Making.</b> Bake a spelt loaf with your children and introduce them to a healthy alternative to white bread while teaching them the skils of the baker. Expect flour fights, sticky fingers, and a fresh loaf to take home for tea.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="chil_3">
		<item>Honey in the City</item>
		<item>The festival will feature a selection of children’s workshops and demonstrations over the weekend, with a focus on introducing children to the world of food in a practical hands on way. Bring your children to discover how honey is made, join in the bread making workshop, and make your own butter and jam.\n<b>Honey in the City</b> Visit Doctor John\'s portable beehives to find out how bees make their honey.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<string-array name="chil_4">
		<item>Jam making / Butter making</item>
		<item>The festival will feature a selection of children’s workshops and demonstrations over the weekend, with a focus on introducing children to the world of food in a practical hands on way. Bring your children to discover how honey is made, join in the bread making workshop, and make your own butter and jam.\n<b>Jam making</b> If your going to bake bread you need something to spread on it. Bring a bag of fresh or frozen fruit and transform it into a scrumptious sticky jam for your healthy loaf.\n<b>Butter making</b> Learn to make butter from milk, and discover where your spread comes from.</item>
	</string-array>
	
	<!-- 
		Other
	 -->
	<string-array name="other_1">
	 	<item>The Harvest Food Market</item>
	 	<item>Spanish Arch is the historical location of Galway\'s once thriving fish market. Sunday will see the area transformed once again into a local farmers harvest market. Market stalls will boast the best of the West local produce including: Vegetables, Meat, Fish, Bread.</item>
	 </string-array>
	 
	 <string-array name="other_2">
	 	<item>Galway\'s Food Community</item>
	 	<item>On Friday and Saturday night there will be a host of stalls along Quay street selling a selection of fantastic local produce. Make your way through the heart of Galway and sample the city’s great atmosphere while tasting everything from smoked salmon and oysters to connemara smoked mountain lamb...beidh ocras orth..agus tart.</item>
	 </string-array>
	 
	 <string-array name="other_3">
	 	<item>The Big Award</item>
	 	<item>A reception in St. Nicholas Church on Saturday will honour one local food hero in recognition of their contribution to food and the Galway Community.</item>
	 </string-array>
	 
	 <string-array name="other_4">
	 	<item>The Feast</item>
	 	<item>Cost - €50 pp\n\nArd Bia will host an dinner celebrating the diversity of Galway\'s Food Culture. Local Produce will feature in a menu specially designed for the festival.</item>
	 </string-array>
</resources>
